https://lushlongboards.com/privacy-policy/

TESTTotal £0.00 · Your cart is empty
Privacy Policy Privacy PolicyHere at Lush we are committed to protecting and preserving the privacy of our visitors when visiting our site or communicating electronically with us.We are GDPR compliant, in line with the latest European Data Protection legislation.Our entire website is encrypted via HTTPS/TLS 256 bit protocols to ensure that any information you do choose to share with us to secure.This Privacy Policy contains an explanation of what happens to personal data that you choose to provide to us, or that we collect from you whilst you visit this site.We do occasionally update this Policy so please do return and review this Policy from time to time.Information We Collect In running and operating this website we may collect and process certain data and information relating to you and your use of this site. This data and information is detailed below:i.Details of visits to our website and the pages and resources that are accessed, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and other communication data that may assist us in understanding how visitors use this website.ii.Information that visitors provide to us as a result of filling in forms on our website, such as when a visitor registers for information or makes a purchase.iii.Information provided to us when our visitors communicate with us electronically for any reason.Use of CookiesCookies are sometimes used to improve the website experience of a visitor to a website. We may sometimes use cookies on this website to record aggregate statistical information about the visitors to our site and the use that our visitors make of the website. When collected this information is used by us to improve our website and further enhance the visitor experience and, may be shared with advertisers. Pease note that no personally identifiable information is recorded.We may also use the cookies to gather information about your general internet use to further assist us in developing or website.  Where used, these cookies are downloaded to your computer automatically. This cookie file is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive and then stored there and transferred to us where appropriate to help us to improve our website and the service that we provide to you. All computers have the ability to decline cookies.  You can easily decline or remove cookies from your computer using the settings within the Internet Options section in your computer control panel.Our advertisers may also use cookies on their website. We have no control over this and you should review the privacy policy of any advertiser that you visit as a result of an advert or link on this website.Use of Your InformationThe information we collect is used for our own use in developing our website and also occasionally by advertisers on this site.   In addition, we may use the information for the following purposes:i.To provide you with information relating to our website, products or our services that you request from us.ii.To provide you with information on other products that we feel may be of interest to you.iii.To meet our contractual obligations to you.iv.To notify you about any changes to our website, including improvements, and service or product changes that may affect our website.You can opt into our newsletter at point of contact, and unsubscribe at any time by following links at the bottom of each mailout.If you are an existing customer, we may contact you with information about goods and services similar to those that you have expressed an interest in previously via our website.If you do not want us to use your data for our use then you wil always have the option to object to such use.Storing Your Personal Data.Information that we collect may on occasion be transferred and stored outside of the European Union for the purpose of supplying our goods or services to you. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will always take all reasonable precautions to make sure that your data remains secure and is handled in accordance with this Privacy Policy.Data that is provided to us is stored on our secure servers. Details relating to any transactions entered into on our site will be encrypted to ensure its safety. The transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure and therefore we cannot guarantee the security of data sent to us electronically and transmission of such data is therefore entirely at your own risk. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password so that you can access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.Disclosing Your InformationWhere applicable, we may disclose your personal information to any member of our group. This includes, where applicable, our subsidiaries, our holding company and its other subsidiaries (if any). We may also disclose your personal information to third parties:i.Where we sell any or all of our business and/or our assets to a third party.ii.Where we are legally required to disclose your information.iii.To assist fraud reduction and minimise credit risks.Third Party LinksYou might find links to third party websites on our website. These websites should have their own privacy policies which you should check. We do not accept any responsibility or liability for their policies whatsoever as we have no control over them.Access to InformationThe Data Protection Act 1998 gives all individuals the right to access personal information that is held about them. You can request a copy of any information that we hold about you. Please note that any request for this information may be subject to payment of £10 which covers our administrative costs.  Please contact us if you wish to make such a request.Contacting UsIf you have any questions or queries relating to this Privacy Policy then please contact us.Awesome! Take me back to the boards!
The Boards
Search for:
Recent posts Skate Solo, Skate Safe The Slayer Speedboard Computational Fluid Dynamics and Downhill Skateboarding… really? Adam’s Freebyrd Robert’s FreebyrdArchivesMarch 2020 (1)February 2020 (1)April 2019 (1)March 2019 (2)February 2019 (1)October 2018 (1)August 2018 (1)July 2018 (3)June 2018 (1)April 2018 (1)February 2018 (1)November 2017 (1)October 2017 (2)September 2017 (2)August 2017 (3)July 2017 (1)June 2017 (2)May 2017 (2)April 2017 (1)March 2017 (1)February 2017 (3)January 2017 (2)December 2016 (2)November 2016 (5)October 2016 (10)September 2016 (29)August 2016 (1)July 2016 (3)June 2016 (3)May 2016 (1)April 2016 (2)March 2016 (2)February 2016 (3)January 2016 (3)December 2015 (1)November 2015 (1)October 2015 (1)September 2015 (1)July 2015 (2)May 2015 (3)April 2015 (2)March 2015 (1)February 2015 (2)December 2014 (1)November 2014 (2)October 2014 (2)September 2014 (9)August 2014 (5)July 2014 (4)June 2014 (2)May 2014 (2)April 2014 (3)March 2014 (2)February 2014 (3)January 2014 (3)December 2013 (2)November 2013 (4)October 2013 (4)September 2013 (3)August 2013 (4)June 2013 (2)May 2013 (8)April 2013 (12)March 2013 (7)February 2013 (4)January 2013 (6)December 2012 (4)November 2012 (12)October 2012 (8)September 2012 (10)August 2012 (5)July 2012 (16)June 2012 (19)May 2012 (7)April 2012 (4)March 2012 (7)February 2012 (5)January 2012 (4)December 2011 (6)November 2011 (6)October 2011 (9)September 2011 (9)August 2011 (7)July 2011 (5)June 2011 (7)May 2010 (1)Please select a country:EuropeUKGermanyFranceSpainNetherlandsItalyAustriaBelgiumPortugalOther EuropeNorth AmericaUSACanadaREST OF WORLDCan’t get hold of our products? Please contact us!!Go To The Cult Wheels WebsiteEuropeUKGermanyFranceSpainNetherlandsItalyAustriaBelgiumPortugalOther EuropeNorth AmericaUSACanadaREST OF WORLDCan’t get hold of our products? Please contact us!!Go To The Sabre Trucks WebsiteEuropeUKGermanyFranceSpainNetherlandsItalyAustriaBelgiumPortugalOther EuropeNorth AmericaUSACanadaREST OF WORLDCan’t get hold of our products? Please contact us!!
